halloweenexpress.com 2007-12-30

# Halloween Costumes and Costume Accessories for Adults, Teens and Kids.

We take your business seriously and use every reasonable precaution necessary to ensure your shopping experience is safe! We want you to be aware of what kind of information we obtain from you, how we use this information, and how you can control its use. By using this site, you consent to this Privacy Policy. 

We operate this web site under the name of HalloweenExpress.com.As such, when you provide information to us, this information may be combined or shared between current or future entities and subsidiaries. 

**What personally identifiable information is collected?**  
In order to provide you superior service, communicate marketing promotions which we believe will be of interest to you, and to administer our business,we may gather the following personal information (except where prohibited by law): salutation, name (first/middle/last), billing and shipping addresses, company name (if applicable), email address, phone/fax number (if applicable), payment type, credit card type/number/expiration date. How this information is used and how we protect information collected from online purchases is explained below.

**How is the collected information used?**  
We use your personally identifiable information to provide superior service in the following areas: to process, fulfill and track online orders; bill your credit card for purchases; respond to your customer service inquiries or requests; provide requested services such as Coupon and Gift Voucher redemption and return/exchange information; offer information regarding products and services based on your interests or past purchases; hold contests, giveaways, drawings and promotions; administer shopping or reward club accounts; conduct and administer surveys; mail marketing/sales material via email or postal mail; set up commercial accounts; sign up for new credit card promotions; or use it for other general business purposes to further enhance our business relationship with you.

To enhance your online experience with us, we may also collect aggregate information as to which pages you visit, search terms used, etc. - in order to measure the effectiveness of our website and identify areas for improvement (product selection, site performance and/or to streamline the purchasing processes).

**How do we use cookies and technology in our website?**  
HalloweenExpress.com sets a cookie on your computer to record certain information during your online visit (session). No personally identifiable information is stored within this cookie. The benefit to you is the ability to save items added to your shopping bag and store them on our server for future reference. These cookies _do not_ gather sensitive information like your name, address, credit card number, etc., if you do not specifically give that information to us voluntarily. If you have given us that information, cookies enable us to recall it (and save you the trouble of entering it all over again) each time you visit our site.

Our web server collects the addresses of the web sites that visitors came from before visiting our site, which browser was used to view our site and search terms entered on our site. Without making use of any personally identifiable information, we may track the pages visited to help us understand how customers use our site. This helps us make decisions on how to create a better experience for you in the future.

At your option, if you delete our cookies, you will limit our ability to personalize the site for your next visit. However, deleting a cookie will not prevent you from visiting our site and making purchases.

**Who are the third party entities with whom we may share your personally identifiable information?**  
We may use third party companies in limited ways. We may provide your information to reputable organizations that help us to fulfill services to you on our behalf. For example, we use may use companies to authorize credit card transactions, to ship packages,, etc. We may provide information to others to help us maintain records and analyze sales data. We use customer information providers to augment and improve the accuracy of our customer database. We hire third parties to distribute postal and email communications with our offers or important information on our behalf. The third party companies we hire are not authorized to use your information for any reason other than to provide the above stated services for which we contract them to perform. 

**How do I opt in/out of HalloweenExpress.com emails or postal mailings?**  
There are various methods for letting us know if you would or would not like to receive HalloweenExpress.com postal or email promotions. (Please note that if you opt out of our email marketing communications, you may still receive business-related communications such as order and shipping confirmations, product recall information or other administrative communications.)

  1. Go to our website (www.HalloweenExpress.com) and click on the “MY ACCOUNT” link found on the top right side of our home page. You will be prompted to enter your username (email address) and password to log-in. Once you have logged in, click on the link that says, "Subscribe or unsubscribe from Newsletters". Check or Un-Check the appropriate box and click "CONTINUE" to apply your changes. 
  2. All promotional emails we send you contain a link allowing you to opt out of these specific emails in the future. Click on the relevant link and follow the simple instructions. 
  3. Write to us and let us know what you would like to receive or not receive. You can send your letter to: 

> HalloweenExpress.com Operations Center  
>  Attn: Email Communication Department  
>  7505 Sussex Drive Lower Level  
>  Florence, KY 41042
> 
> **Note:** Please be sure to include your full name, address, phone number and email address and tell us specifically which type of marketing communication you wish to receive or stop receiving. This will allow us to correctly identify you in our systems and process your request. 

  4. You can also fax your letter to us (be sure to include the information requested above) at 859.818.0802.   

If you opted out of receiving our postal or email marketing communications, please allow us a reasonable period of time to honor your request, as some promotions may already be in process. For email subscriptions, please allow up to 10 business days for us to make the requested changes. Removal from our print advertising list may take up to 4 - 5 weeks, depending on the mailing cycle updating process. 

**How do we protect the security of your HalloweenExpress.com order information?**  
We are concerned about your privacy and the security of your important personal information. We always use industry standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving any data that you exchange with our site. We employ the same industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology that is used by major banks and stock brokerage firms to conduct business via the Internet. This encryption procedure "scrambles" the information you send us and makes online transactions extremely safe.

When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information, such as financial information, you will be redirected to a secure server and we will notify you, depending on the type of browser you are using, through a pop-up screen or a yellow "padlock" icon displayed in the lower portion of the browser window. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you via this site. 

We have partnered with Authorize.Net, a leading payment gateway since 1996, to offer safe and secure credit card transactions for our customers. The Authorize.Net Payment Gateway manages the complex routing of sensitive customer information through the credit card and electronic check processing networks (see an [online payments diagram](http://www.authorize.net/resources/howitworksdiagram/)). The company adheres to strict industry standards for payment processing, including: 

  * 128-bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology for secure Internet Protocol (IP) transactions. 

  * Industry leading encryption hardware and software methods and security protocols to protect customer information. 

  * Compliance with the Payment Card Industry (PCI) Data Security Standard.

For additional information regarding the privacy of your sensitive cardholder data, please read the [Authorize.Net Privacy Policy](http://www.authorize.net/company/privacy/).

We are registered with the Authorize.Net Verified Merchant Seal program. 

**How do we handle information related to children?**  
This site is not intended or designed to attract children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly or intentionally obtain any personally identifiable information from any person we know to be under the age of 13. 

**How am I notified of Privacy Policy changes?**  
As we continue to grow our businesses and improve our services, we reserve the right to change or modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If there are changes or additions, we will post those changes here or in other formats we deem acceptable, so that you are aware of such changes. If this Privacy Policy changes in such a way that your personally identifiable information may be used or shared in a different manner, you will be given the opportunity to opt-out of having your information used or shared in that new manner. If you are concerned about how your information is used, please check back at this site periodically. 

**Disclosure exceptions:**  
Notwithstanding the above policies, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information to appropriate third parties if we are required to do so by law or we believe that such action is necessary to comply with legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order; to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website; to protect our rights and property; or during emergencies, such as when we believe someone’s physical safety is at risk.

In addition, as we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer information, email addresses, and visitor information are generally among the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or any dissolution, including, but not limited to, a bankruptcy proceeding.

The effective date of this Privacy Policy is January 1, 2005. It was last updated on August 15, 2006.  

To view the Terms & Conditions of using this website, [click here](http://www.halloweenexpress.com/terms_of_use.php).
